Hello friends, welcome
to our channel today we are going to talk about
which is the best insurance company
for two wheelers yes we are going to talk about
today in this video there is a famous one there is
only fog and darshan I will tell you that if you
take Raghubir to the market then you will
get a lot of these machines, although I
could not provide it in the showroom but it is
not compulsory that you go to the showroom and get
insurance, you can get insurance from any company by
taking the chassis and engine number of your state
now let me tell you which
companies there is Bharti AXA, HDFC Agro,
Bajaj also, ICICI Lombard, there are
many other companies
which provide two wheeler insurance
and if I talk about the
increase, the most
oil liner is used in two wheelers, which such
insurance company is the law minister of
west expensive which means the best will
help you in making your insurance claim in a very fast manner, if there is
damage to your vehicle then
how much time will it take for the telescope plane, how much period will it take  Whether it is
cashless or not,
visibility and availability is everywhere. This
appointment is only of the insurance company. Where does the
problem come from? Where does it not come from? This is the
root of all the problems and the wave of power.
After looking at all these tractors, if I see any company, my
personal experience is telling me friends that
I have done a lot of calculations, a lot of
meaning, I talked to people,
talked to showrooms, only then I came to know that
ICICI Lombard is
used a lot in two wheeler insurance.
Loot check. Let me tell you again, if two wheeler
insurance is used the most, then potato sexy is long, then this is the
data till the villain. It is
possible that there may be other companies in four wheeler and there may be more,
but because the
girl who keeps getting Tata inside is
saying this, Delhi-NCR is the place
for me. ICICI
Lombard is on top in this. Anuj Ahiravan trousers
robbers of India, 822 but will maintain a
good position in it.
Billion Center which will go to the number one when I go to the bathroom.  So let me
tell you that ICICI Lombard is the
number one insurance company for two wheelers. It is
number one all over India. I have
n't used it yet, friends, but it is
number one in this field, so it wo
n't leave other places as well. So, being at number one is not the
only thing that matters. Its rate is not
too expensive either. And
how can the policy and accurate treatment be given to the
couple. After that, the
claim cover is also quite
good. You won't face much problem.
You will also need the commission's clarification. You should get it
cleared. You are
looking for an insurance policy only for your name
because
five
insurance policies are mandatory in India. So, I
hope if you want to get such insurance, that is, for the
name of the person in the media, then
take it from any company. Search online.
You will find these companies. There will be no
such problem for you. But if you
want a person who can do good work, who can
work really well, then you should invest today. Many other companies have worked,
but this facility of time is available in
Indian  The company also gives full service to the Sangh,
all the companies,
but if you want to talk about time in some Mahakal
Galaxy, then how can I get
Indian media after sales service without 15 Aditya, then I am
just telling you about it,
which goes towards ICC award, so
friends, like the video, if you like it,
share it and
subscribe to the channel and press the bell icon,
hello friends.